A Guide to the Davis & Associates Architectural Drawing Collection, 1925-1985 (bulk, 1954-1985)
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Rockingham County
  - Studio Addition, Mr. & Mrs. C. E. May, 1958, 2 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #5803
  - Educational Building for Cook's Creek Presbyterian Church, 1964, 52 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #6109
  - Melville Footwear Manufacturing Distribution Center, 1976, 1 Sheet (Box 28)
  - New Building for the McGaheysville Full Gospel Assembly, 1982, 4 Sheets (Box 28)
  - Proposed Addition to the Branch Bank of the Valley National Bank 1972, 2 Sheets (Box 28)
  - Addition & Alterations to Home Office, Shenandoah Valley Electric Cooperative, 1974, 3 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #7419
  - Addition to the Massanutten Vocational Technical Center, 1976, 13 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #7430
  - Alterations to Home Office, Shenandoah Valley Electric Cooperative, 1983, 1 Sheet (Box 28)
    Comm. #8304
  - Addition to John Wayland Intermediate School, 1969, 13 Sheets (Box 29)
  - The Plains District Elementary School, 1971, 2 Sheets (Box 29)
  - Proposed Addition to Bridgewater Home for the Aging, 1972, 78 Sheets (Box 29)
    Comm. #6906
  - Time-Sharing Townhouses for Massanutten Village, Inc., 1978, 1 Sheet (Box 29)
    Comm. #7802-A
  - Site Development--Rockingham Publishing Co., 1979, 8 Sheets (Box 29)
  - Massanutten Vocational-Technical Center, 1972, 86 Sheets (Box 29)
    Comm. #6824
  - Proposed Residence for Mr. and Mrs. Jerry Sullivan, 1980, 7 Sheets (Box 29)
    Comm. #8003
  - Proposed Building for Hensley Sales/Service, 1973, 5 Sheets (Box 29)
    Comm. #7327
  - Montevideo Intermediate and Montevideo High School, 1975, 4 Sheets (Box 29)
    Comm. #7532
  - Intermediate School Addition to Montevideo High School, 1965, 37 Sheets (Box 30)
    Comm. #6417
  - Intermediate School Addition to Elkton High School, 1965, 24 Sheets (Box 30)
    Comm. #6416
  - John C. Myers Intermediate School, 1963, 21 Sheets (Box 30)
  - Addition to B.Way High 1963, 1 Sheet (Box 30)
    Comm. #6312
  - Tool Shed for County Schools, 1 Sheet (Box 30)
  - Sketch of Sign for Pleasant Valley School 1963, 1 Sheet (Box 30)
  - Proposed Elementary School 1962, 1 Sheet (Box 30)
  - Alterations to Home Office, Shenandoah Valley Electric Cooperative, 1961, 16 Sheets (Box 30)
  - Outside Stair for R. J. Keyser House, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 30)
    Comm. #6812
  - Rockingham Poultry Marketing Cooperative, Inc., 1960, 1 Sheet (Box 30)
  - Map of the C. A. Obaugh & R. B. Neff Properties, Central District, Rockingham Co., 1961, 1 Sheet (Box 30)
  - Shop Addition to Elkton High School, 1 Sheet (Box 30)
  - Residence for Dr. & Mrs. Dale Ulrich, 1967, 1 Sheet (Box 30)
    Comm. #6728
  - Residence for Mr. & Mrs. Dick Keyser, 1966, 2 Sheets (Box 30)
    Comm. #6628
  - Addition & Alterations to Mt. Sinai EUB Church, 1967, 8 Sheets (Box 30)
    Comm. #6712
  - Residence for Mr. & Mrs. Sappington, 1967, 3 Sheets (Box 30)
    Comm. #6730
  - Additions & Alterations to Nelson Huffman House, 1 Sheet (Box 30)
  - Addition #2 for Planters Bank, 1967, 2 Sheets (Box 30)
    Comm. #6711
  - New Building for the Elkton Volunteer Fire Company, Inc., 1967, 5 Sheets (Box 30)
    Comm. #6718
  - Alterations and Additions to the Planters Bank, 1962, 27 Sheets (Box 30)
    Comm. #6119
  - Addition to R. D. C. #1 Building (Metro Pants Company, Inc.), 1964, 1 Sheet (Box 31)
    Comm. #6420
  - R. D. C. #1 Building 1958, 5 Sheets (Box 31)
    Comm. #5837
  - Bridgewater-Metro Metro Pants Co., 1965, 11 Sheets (Box 31)
    Comm. #6531
  - Additions & Alterations to Metro Pants Mfg. Co., 1970, 28 Sheets (Box 31)
  - Manufacturing Plant Building for H. D. Lee Company Inc., 1959, 18 Sheets (Box 31)
  - Additions and Alterations to the Elkton Elementary School, 1970, 1 Sheet (Box 31)
  - Warehouse Addition to Metro Pants, 1976, 2 Sheets (Box 31)
  - Sketch of Valley National Bank, 1 Sheet (Box 31)
  - Motel for Massanutten Development Co., 1978, 19 Sheets (Box 31)
    Comm. #7806
  - Office Building for Massanutten Development Co., 1978, 6 Sheets (Box 31)
    Comm. #7811
  - Time-Sharing Townhouses for Massanutten Village, Inc., 1978, 23 Sheets (Box 31)
    Comm. #7802
  - Time-Sharing Townhouses for Massanutten Village, Inc., 1978, 29 Sheets (Box 31)
    Comm. #7802-A,B
  - Time-Sharing Townhouses for Massanutten Village, Inc., 1980, 1 Sheet (Box 31)
    Comm. #8007
  - Time-Sharing Townhouses for Massanutten Village, Inc., 2 Sheets (Box 31)
    Comm. #8448
  - Office Building for Massanutten Village, Inc., 1979, 22 Sheets (Box 31)
    Comm. #7853
  - Proposed Second Floor Expansion for Massanutten Lodge, 1978, 2 Sheets (Box 31)
    Comm. #7852
  - "The Peak" Mezzanine Expansion for Massanutten Village, Inc., 1979, 2 Sheets (Box 31)
    Comm. #7923
  - Fire Stair Addition for Main Lodge for Massanutten Village, Inc., 1979, 1 Sheet (Box 31)
    Comm. #7922
  - Maps of Massanutten Development Company Property, 3 Sheets (Box 31)
  - Dayton Mennonite Church, 5 Sheets (Box 31)
  - Additions and Alterations to John C. Myers Intermediate School, 1975, 27 Sheets (Box 31)
  - Swimming Pool Addition to Alumni Gymnasium, 1979, 95 Sheets (Box 32)
    Comm. #7531
  - Library Exterior Plans, 1962, 8 Sheets (Box 32)
  - Student Union Building, 1967, 25 Sheets (Box 32)
    Comm. #6526
  - Bridgewater College, 1963-1966, 25 Sheets (Box 33)
    Comm. #BC
  - Alterations to Union Building, 1967, 3 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Addition-Alterations to Cole Hall, 1972, 40 Sheets (Box 33)
    Comm. #7203
  - Alterations to Art Department, 1975, 4 Sheets (Box 33)
    Comm. #7528
  - New Pool for Gym 1975, 4 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Proposed Administrative-Classroom Building, 1975, 5 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Additions and Alterations to Memorial Hall, 1975, 1 Sheet (Box 33)
    Comm. #7534
  - (Additions and Alterations to) Yount Hall, 1975, 9 Sheets (Box 33)
    Comm. #7523
  - Food Facility Equipment List and Utility Schedule, 1967, 1 Sheet (Box 33)
    Comm. #1423-4
  - Proposed Dormitory/Apartments, 1979, 34 Sheets (Box 33)
    Comm. #7821
  - Faculty Apartment House, 1955, 9 Sheets (Box 33)
    Comm. #5522
  - Men's Dormitory Area, 1959, 1 Sheet (Box 33)
    Comm. #304-A2
  - Proposed Master Plan, 1967, 1 Sheet (Box 33)
  - Proposed Greenhouse Addition to BC Science Building, 1 Sheet (Box 33)
  - Proposed Building/Library Sites, 1958, 2 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Study for Master Plan, 1958, 1 Sheet (Box 33)
  - Girls' Dormitory, 1962, 8 Sheets (Box 33)
    Comm. #6125
  - Boiler House, 1963, 3 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Men's Dormitory, 1963, 6 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Planting Plans: Library, Girls' Dormitory, Daleville, 1963, 5 Sheets (Box 33)
  - An Entrance Sign for Bridgewater College, 1963, 2 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Student Union, 4 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Map of Bridgewater College, 1963, 1 Sheet (Box 33)
  - Bulletin Board, 1965, 1 Sheet (Box 33)
  - Home Economics Building, 1967, 9 Sheets (Box 33)
    Comm. #6719
  - Bridgewater College Plot Plan, 1967, 3 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Blue Ridge Hall Women's Dormitory, 1969, 8 Sheets (Box 33)
    Comm. #7115
  - Bowman Hall, 1970, 3 Sheets (Box 33)
    Comm. #7029
  - Rebecca Hall, 3 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Science Building, 3 Sheets (Box 33)
  - New Girls' Dorm, 7 Sheets (Box 33)
  - Bridgewater College Library, 1961, 15 Sheets (Box 33)
- Augusta County
  - Elliott Knob Transmitter Station (Revised Project) for Shenandoah Valley Educational Television Corp., 1967, 12 Sheets (Box 34)
    Comm. #6715
  - Pool & Enclosure, Cletus Houff Residence, 1968, 4 Sheets (Box 34)
    Comm. #6820
  - Doctors' Offices for Weyers Cave, VA, 1973, 4 Sheets (Box 34)
    Comm. #7308
  - Plant for Degesch America, 1977, 49 Sheets (Box 34)
    Comm. #7714
  - Roof Replacement, Blue Ridge Community College, 1981, 1 Sheet (Box 34)
    Comm. #8127
  - Roof Replacement, Strader Hall, Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, 1981, 1 Sheet (Box 34)
    Comm. #8125
  - Additions-Alterations to Howard Johnson Restaurant, 1969, 19 Sheets (Box 34)
    Comm. #6904
  - Proposed Building for Sunlite Plastic, Inc., 1971, 11 Sheets (Box 34)
    Comm. #7119
  - Proposed Staunton Office for Old Dominion Savings and Loan, 1977, 37 Sheets (Box 34)
    Comm. #7708
  - Office Building for Degesch America, Inc., 1979, 36 Sheets (Box 34)
    Comm. #7912
  - Industrial Rehabilitation Building, Western State Hospital, 1971, 10 Sheets (Box 35)
  - Renovations and Repairs, Western State Hospital, 1975, 45 Sheets (Box 35)
    Comm. #7329
  - Active Treatment Building, Western State Hospital, 1973, 66 Sheets (Box 35)
    Comm. #7217
  - Alterations to Darden Hall, Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, 1983, 9 Sheets (Box 35)
    Comm. #8324
  - Western State Warehouse, Maintenance Shops, Motor Pool, 17 Sheets (Box 35)
    Comm. #8114
  - Beverly Manor School, 1928, 21 Sheets (Box 36)
    Comm. #354
  - Staunton Street Map, 1 Sheet (Box 36)
  - Sketches/Memos for Wilson Shopping Center-Staunton, 1 Sheet (Box 36)
  - US Post Office, Weyers Cave, 1960, 10 Sheets (Box 36)
    Comm. #6006
  - Site Plan for L. Greif and Bro. Inc., 1961, 1 Sheet (Box 36)
  - Waynesboro YMCA, 1965, 12 Sheets (Box 36)
    Comm. #6518
  - Inn-Restaurant for Dean Wilson, 1968, 5 Sheets (Box 36)
  - Wilson Project, 1965, 27 Sheets (Box 36)
  - Residence for Mr. & Mrs. R. B. Smith, 1961, 27 Sheets (Box 36)
    Comm. #6110
  - Stuarts Draft Branch for Rockingham National Bank, 1982, 42 Sheets (Box 36)
    Comm. #8021
  - Staunton Office of the Old Dominion Savings and Loan, 1977, 1 Sheet (Box 36)
  - Weyers Cave Manufacturing Plant for Cerro Metal Products, 1978, 23 Sheets (Box 37)
    Comm. #7720
  - Dawbarn Division-W. R. Grace & Company Master Plan for Future Development, 1965, 1967, 3 Sheets (Box 37)
  - Phase V Addition to Dawbarn Division W. R. Grace & Co., 1966, 37 Sheets (Box 37)
    Comm. #6606
  - Research-Development Addition to Dawbarn Division, Thiokol Chemical Corp., 1969, 16 Sheets (Box 37)
    Comm. #6840
  - Office Remodeling for Dawbarn Division, Thiokol Chemical Corp., 1969, 7 Sheets (Box 37)
    Comm. #6931
  - Additions to Dawbarn Division and other unlabeled sheets, 1969, 19 Sheets (Box 37)
  - Addition to Dawbarn Division, W. R. Grace & Co, 1964, 17 Sheets (Box 37)
    Comm. #6424
  - Phase IV Addition to Dawbarn Division, W. R. Grace & Co, 1966, 10 Sheets (Box 37)
    Comm. #6601
  - Phase III Addition to Dawbarn Division, W. R. Grace & Co, 1965, 8 Sheets (Box 37)
    Comm. #6537
  - Phase I Additions to Dawbarn Division, W. R. Grace & Co, 1965, 17 Sheets (Box 37)
    Comm. #6507
  - Map; near Shenandoah Valley Regional Airport, 1971, 1 Sheet (Box 38)
  - Addition to Blue Ridge Community College, 1972, 113 Sheets (Box 38)
    Comm. #7212
  - Vocational Shop Building--Staunton Campus for BRCC, 1 Sheet (Box 38)
    Comm. #7214
  - Proposed Danish Candy Plant, 1977, 5 Sheets (Box 38)
    Comm. #7719
  - Staunton Office for Virginia National Bank, 1977, 52 Sheets (Box 38)
    Comm. #7617
  - Augusta Co-Operative Farm Bureau, 1956, 10 Sheets (Box 38)
    Comm. #5601
  - Proposed Remodeling-Addition to Verona Office, Rockingham National Bank, 1978, 61 Sheets (Box 38)
    Comm. #7832
  - Joint City-County Office Project, 1974, 31 Sheets (Box 38)
  - Degesch America, Inc., 1977, 1 Sheet (Box 39)
  - Office Building for Degesch America, Inc., 1979, 58 Sheets (Box 39)
    Comm. #7732
  - Warehouse for Smith's Transfer, 1958, 1 Sheet (Box 39)
  - Physical Activities Building for Waynesboro YMCA, 1966, 73 Sheets (Box 39)
    Comm. #6513
  - Stuarts Draft Branch for Rockingham National Bank, 1982, 7 Sheets (Box 39)
  - Blue Ridge Trailer Park, 1 Sheet (Box 39)
  - Improvements to Country Residence of Mr. Zane Showker, 1977, 13 Sheets (Box 39)
- Page County
  - Renovations and Details, Leggett's Dept. Store, 1957, 31 Sheets (Box 15)
    Comm. #5532
  - Alterations to Leggett's Dept. Store, 1959, 1 Sheet (Box 15)
    Comm. #5808
  - Page County Map, 1 Sheet (Box 15)
  - Page County High School, 3 Sheets (Box 15)
    Comm. #7428
  - Stanley Elementary, 1974, 2 Sheets (Box 15)
  - Addition to Grove Hill Elementary School, 1974, 2 Sheets (Box 15)
  - Springfield Elementary, 1974, 2 Sheets (Box 15)
  - Luray High School, 1974, 2 Sheets (Box 15)
  - Luray Elementary, 1974, 2 Sheets (Box 15)
  - Shenandoah Elementary, 1976, 1 Sheet (Box 15)
  - Proposed Residence for Mr. & Mrs. Bennie Huffman, 1969, 1 Sheet (Box 15)
    Comm. #6925
  - Proposed Drug Store for W. McKay, 1967, 1 Sheet (Box 15)
  - Schewels Furniture Store, 1974, 17 Sheets (Box 15)
    Comm. #7331
- Shenandoah County
  - Shenandoah County Doctor's Offices, 35 Sheets (Box 41)
    Comm. #7123
  - Addition to Woodstock Elementary School, 2 Sheets (Box 41)
  - Cadet Road Apartments for Central Valley Construction Co., 1971, 9 Sheets (Box 41)
    Comm. #7102
  - Stonewall Primary School, 1973, 40 Sheets (Box 41)
    Comm. #7132
  - Woodstock Office for the Old Dominion Savings and Loan Association, 1974, 38 Sheets (Box 41)
    Comm. #7404
  - Cottages for Bryce Mountain, 7403, 9 Sheets (Box 41)
    Comm. #7403
  - Driver Residence, 1960, 6 Sheets (Box 41)
    Comm. #6004
  - Remodeling for Thorington Construction Co., 1958, 1 Sheet (Box 41)
    Comm. #5814
  - Remodeling First National Bank of Shenandoah, 1959, 10 Sheets (Box 41)
    Comm. #5826
  - Addition to School Bus Garage for Shenandoah County, 1967, 15 Sheets (Box 41)
  - Mt. Jackson Mennonite Church, 1977, 15 Sheets (Box 41)
    Comm. #7716
  - Residence for John E. Simmons, 3 Sheets (Box 41)
  - Enclosure Wall, Triplett Business and Technical Institute, 1981, 3 Sheets (Box 41)
  - Addition to Gordon Bowman Residence, 13 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #7208
  - Proposed Shopping Center and Motel, 1975, 3 Sheets (Box 42)
  - Alterations to Hadley Hall for Shenandoah Valley Academy, 1981, 3 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #8124
  - Route 81 from Rockingham County Line to Woodstock, 1958, 2 Sheets (Box 42)
  - Mt. Jackson Office for the Shenandoah Valley Electric Co-Op, 1970, 13 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #6920
  - Plans for Grace Memorial Church, 1959, 4 Sheets (Box 42)
  - Remodeling of Bushong House, Civil War Battlefield Mem., 1967, 8 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #6704
  - Fire Station, 1967, 11 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #6720
  - School Bus Garage for Shenandoah County, 1967, 2 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #6717
  - Addition & Alterations to The National Bank of Woodstock, 1965, 22 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #6401
  - Shenandoah County Courthouse Remodeling, 1977, 53 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #7630
  - Miscellaneous Shenvallee Plans, 18 Sheets (Box 42)
  - Alterations and Additions to Shenvallee Lodge, 1964, 46 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #6216
  - Motor Lodge Addition for Shenvallee Lodge, 1967, 17 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #6617
  - Alterations and Additions to Shenvallee Lodge, 1967, 9 Sheets (Box 42)
    Comm. #6618
  - Strasburg Shopping Center, 1972, 1 Sheet (Box 43)
    Comm. #7220
  - Office Remodeling for Sullivan Mechanical, 1972, 1 Sheet (Box 43)
    Comm. #7204
  - Shenandoah County Memorial Hospital, 1978, 10 Sheets (Box 43)
    Comm. #7722
  - Cardiac/Intensive Care Unit for Shenandoah County Memorial Hospital, 1976, 6 Sheets (Box 43)
    Comm. #7425
  - Miscellaneous Shenandoah County Memorial Hospital, 7 Sheets (Box 43)
  - Phase III Operation & Food Service Addition to Shenandoah County Memorial Hospital, 1985, 8 Sheets (Box 43)
    Comm. #8428
  - Phase II Administrative Addition and Alterations to Shenandoah County Memorial Hospital, 1984, 1 Sheet (Box 43)
    Comm. #8408
  - Tri-Valley Nursing Home, 1967, 1 Sheet (Box 43)
    Comm. #6822
  - Additions and Alterations to Tripplett Business and Technical Institute, 1975, 61 Sheets (Box 43)
    Comm. #7414
  - New Office for Farmers Bank of Edinburg, 1974, 33 Sheets (Box 43)
    Comm. #7339
  - Central Primary School, 1975, 73 Sheets (Box 43)
    Comm. #7412
  - Drive-Up Window for Virginia National Bank, 1975, 6 Sheets (Box 44)
    Comm. #7431
  - Sewage Disposal System for John E. Simmons--Residence, 1959, 1 Sheet (Box 44)
  - Strasburg Primary School, 1970, 49 Sheets (Box 44)
    Comm. #6908
  - Service Building for New Market Battlefield Memorial, 1984, 9 Sheets (Box 44)
    Comm. #8318
  - 1970 Additions to Shenandoah Telephone Co., 1970, 9 Sheets (Box 44)
  - Additions & Alterations to Shenandoah Telephone Co., 1970, 17 Sheets (Box 44)
    Comm. #7012
  - Additions & Alterations to Shenandoah Telephone Co., 1973, 25 Sheets (Box 44)
    Comm. #7311
  - Shenandoah County Health Center, 1970, 29 Sheets (Box 44)
    Comm. #6836
  - Proposed Additions/Alterations to Shenandoah County Memorial Hospital, 1979, 39 Sheets (Box 45)
    Comm. #7911
  - Offices for J. W. Rosenberger, 1968, 6 Sheets (Box 45)
    Comm. #6831
  - Tri-Valley Nursing Home, 1969, 44 Sheets (Box 45)
- Photographs
  - Walker Manufacturing Construction Photos, 1971, 84 Photos (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Site of Picture: Harrisonburg
  - Office Building for Keeler, Phibbs, & Co., 1981, 19 Photos (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Computer Center for Rockingham National Bank, 1972, 7 Photos (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Kavanaugh Housing for the Elderly, 1977, 16 Photos (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Municipal Building, 1976, 8 Photos (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Included with Mini-Facility for Rockingham National Bank; Grocery or General Store, 1976, 2 Photos (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Community Mennonite Church, 1 Photo (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Warehouse Addition to Metro Pants, 1976, 26 Photos (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Site of Picture: Bridgewater, Rockingham County
  - Aerial Photographs of Weyers Cave Manufacturing Plant for Cerro Metal Products, 1978, 2 Photos (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    Site of Picture: Augusta County
  - Sign for Degesch America, Inc, 1 Photo (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Grace Memorial Church (now Grace United Church of Christ), 1959, 6 Photos (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Site of Picture: Mt. Jackson, Shenandoah County
  - Shenandoah County Courthouse, 1977, 26 Photos (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Site of Picture: Shenandoah County
  - Positives and Negatives of Wilson and Maury, 6 Photos (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Additions and Alterations to Rockingham Memorial Hopsital, 1 Film (Box 1, Folder 8)